[
    {
      "question": "Who sang the title song for the latest Bond film, No Time to Die?",
      "options": ["Adele", "Sam Smith", "Billie Eilish"],
      "correctAnswer": "Billie Eilish"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which flies a green, white, and orange (in that order) tricolor flag?",
      "options": ["Ireland", "Ivory Coast", "Italy"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ireland"
    },
    {
      "question": "What company makes the Xperia model of smartphone?",
      "options": ["Samsung", "Sony", "Nokia"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sony"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city is home to the Brandenburg Gate?",
      "options": ["Vienna", "Zurich", "Berlin"],
      "correctAnswer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a fruit?",
      "options": ["Rhubarb", "Tomatoes", "Avocados"],
      "correctAnswer": "Rhubarb"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was the first example of paper money used?",
      "options": ["China", "Turkey", "Greece"],
      "correctAnswer": "China"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is generally considered the inventor of the motor car?",
      "options": ["Henry Ford", "Karl Benz", "Henry M. Leland"],
      "correctAnswer": "Karl Benz"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you were looking at Iguazu Falls, on what continent would you be?",
      "options": ["Asia", "Africa", "South America"],
      "correctAnswer": "South America"
    },
    {
      "question": "What number was the Apollo mission that successfully put a man on the moon for the first time in human history?",
      "options": ["Apollo 11", "Apollo 12", "Apollo 13"],
      "correctAnswer": "Apollo 11"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following languages has the longest alphabet?",
      "options": ["Greek", "Russian", "Arabic"],
      "correctAnswer": "Russian"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the lead singer of the band The Who?",
      "options": ["Roger Daltrey", "Don Henley", "Robert Plant"],
      "correctAnswer": "Roger Daltrey"
    },
    {
      "question": "What spirit is used in making a Tom Collins?",
      "options": ["Vodka", "Rum", "Gin"],
      "correctAnswer": "Gin"
    },
    {
      "question": "The fear of insects is known as what?",
      "options": ["Entomophobia", "Arachnophobia", "Ailurophobia"],
      "correctAnswer": "Entomophobia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of the Franco-British supersonic commercial plane that operated from 1976-2003?",
      "options": ["Accord", "Concorde", "Mirage"],
      "correctAnswer": "Concorde"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which horoscope sign is a fish?",
      "options": ["Aquarius", "Cancer", "Pisces"],
      "correctAnswer": "Pisces"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the largest US state (by landmass)?",
      "options": ["Texas", "Alaska", "California"],
      "correctAnswer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which app has the most total users?",
      "options": ["TikTok", "Snapchat", "Instagram"],
      "correctAnswer": "Instagram"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Game of Thrones character is known as the Young Wolf?",
      "options": ["Robb Stark", "Arya Stark", "Sansa Stark"],
      "correctAnswer": "Robb Stark"
    },
    {
      "question": "What city hosted the 2002 Olympic Games?",
      "options": ["Tokyo", "Beijing", "Sydney"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sydney"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many plays do people (generally) believe that Shakespeare wrote?",
      "options": ["27", "37", "47"],
      "correctAnswer": "37"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following was considered one of the Seven Ancient Wonders?",
      "options": ["Colosseum", "Great Wall of China", "Colossus of Rhodes"],
      "correctAnswer": "Colossus of Rhodes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who directed the Academy Award-winning movie, Gladiator?",
      "options": ["Ridley Scott", "James Cameron", "Steven Soderbergh"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ridley Scott"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long did dinosaurs live on the earth?",
      "options": ["100-150 million years", "150-200 million years", "200+ million years"],
      "correctAnswer": "150-200 million years"
    },
    {
      "question": "What Italian city is famous for its system of canals?",
      "options": ["Rome", "Naples", "Venice"],
      "correctAnswer": "Venice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the strongest muscle in the human body?",
      "options": ["Jaw", "Heart", "Glutes"],
      "correctAnswer": "Jaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the longest-running Broadway show ever?",
      "options": ["Les Miserable", "The Lion King", "The Phantom of the Opera"],
      "correctAnswer": "The Phantom of the Opera"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was tea invented?",
      "options": ["England", "USA", "China"],
      "correctAnswer": "China"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was the earliest documented case of the Spanish flu?",
      "options": ["USA", "Spain", "Mexico"],
      "correctAnswer": "USA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following languages is NOT driven from Latin?",
      "options": ["French", "Portuguese", "English"],
      "correctAnswer": "English"
    },
    {
      "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger was married to a member of what famous US political family?",
      "options": ["The Kennedys", "The Bushes", "The Rockefellers"],
      "correctAnswer": "The Kennedys"
    }
  ]
  